siteexplorer.info 2019-03-21

# Privacy Policy

If you have any questions about our privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us. 

At SiteExplorer.Info, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by SiteExplorer.Info and how it is used.   
This statement includes siteexplorer.info and all subdomains within. 

**Log Files**

Like most other Web sites, SiteExplorer.Info makes use of log files. The (IP) addresses, type Of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date / time stamp, referring / exit Pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, Movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and Other such information is not Identifiable. 

**Web traffic Analytics**

All of the information in Log Files is also transmitted to Google Analytics. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

SiteExplorer.Info uses cookies to store information about visitors Preferences, record user-specific information on which pages Visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other Information that the visitor sends via their browser.   
If you want to disable cookies, you can do so through your individual browser Options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web Browsers can be found at the respective websites. 

SiteExplorer.Info only shares personal information with other companies Individuals outside of SiteExplorer.Info in the following limited Circumstances:  
 -We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing Of any sensitive personal information.  
 -We provide such information to our Subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted The purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that These parts Compliance with this Privacy Policy And security measures.   
-We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of Such information is reasonably necessary to  
 (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request,  
 (b) enforce Applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations,  
 (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical Issues,  
 (d) protect against the rights, property or safety of SiteExplorer.Info, its users or the public as required or permitted by law. 

If SiteExplorer.Info becomes involved in merger, acquisition, or any form Of sale of some or all of its assets, we will ensure the confidentiality of any Personal information Personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy Policy. 

**Information Security**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to Or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include Appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against Unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. 

**Changes to this Statement**

Please note that this content may change from time to time. We will post the newest one on this page
